Megadeth
The Conjuring
Welcome to our sanguinary sect of worship
Feel at home in our black conventicle
As we anathematise all those who oppose us
Don't summon the Devil
Don't call the priests
If you need the strength
The conjuring
Obey!
Behold, the flames rise from the compass' cardinal points
Burn the sacred oil, and with the ashes you'll anoint
Arrange the symbols of the wizard and magician
Light the candles, place the parchment paper in position
Between its leaves place the lash from a black cat's eye
A straw of a broom, fold, and burn, and centralise
Don't summon the devil
Don't call the priests
If you need the strength
Then conjure me
I am the Devil's advocate
A salesman, if you will
You know my name
I met your father years ago
I gave him what he'd please
He called my name
And you'll do the same
I'm claiming what is mine by right
It's time to close the deal
You're bought and sold
Bought and sold
Come join me in my infernal depths
Mephisto's hall of fame
I've got your soul
The conjuring...
Obey!